Contact

shashank.shekhar1912@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ shashank1912 (LinkedIn) stonedsanta.in (Company) www.quora.com/profile/Shashank-Shekhar-221 (Blog) www.instagram.com/ trippy_entrepreneur/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Public Speaking Entrepreneurship Sales

Languages

English

Marwari

Hindi

Honors-Awards

Winners

Winners at a B-Plan competition

Publications

How I scored an ROI of 322 percent for my startup by spending one night with 400 Uber drivers

Shashank Shekhar

Founder, Stoned Santa | Personalized Gifts | Quora - 5M Views Bengaluru

Summary

I am the Founder of Stoned Santa, an IIM Bangalore incubated startup that specializes in curating Personalized Gifting Experiences for individuals and Brands, by providing a platform to artists and creators to earn and get recognized for their work.

I started my entrepreneurial journey during my Final Year of Engineering, and I have always believed in harnessing the Potential of Storytelling.

Experience

Stoned Santa
Chief Executive Officer
June 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka

Stoned Santa is an IIM-Bangalore incubated startup that specializes in curating Personalized Gifting Experiences for individuals and brands by enabling artists and creators to come together to create Personalized Art.

The Climber Youth Mentor September 2019 - Present (1 year) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

I share my entrepreneurial learnings through 8 LIVE Discussions every month with college students who aspire to startup in their future. The LIVE discussions walk them through a process that helps them see things about the world of startups with a fresh perspective, and give them content that is actionable.

Discussion 1 - What is a startup? What's common between all startups? Startup Myths.

Discussion 2 - A lot of Examples to understand Startup as a concept better.

Page 1 of 2

Discussion 3 - How to find a Problem? Why finding Problems is important?

Discussion 4 - How to find people who face these problems? How to approach and build an MVP

Discussion 5 - Documenting the ideas and building a structure - Creation of Lean Model Canvas

Discussion 6 - How to find a team? How to find potential users/customers? Marketing 101

Discussion 7 - How to manage finances? Do I need funding? A little about numbers

Discussion 8 - Build a B-Plan Pitch deck, and get ready to move.

All the discussions mentioned above are introductory, and the prime focus is to help them develop the mindset and the understanding of what it takes to execute ideas and build a company out of it.

Atal Innovation Mission
Mentor
February 2020 - Present (7 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Education

SRM University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2013 - 2017)

Indian Institute of Management Bangalore Startup Incubation, Entrepreneurship (2017)

Delhi Public School - India · (2007 - 2013)